Guide to the Diane Sherrer collection, 1969-2009.
Sherrer, Diane collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Diane Sherrer collection, 1969-2009.
4754
Diane Sherrer
8.4 cubic feet.
Manuscripts, Newspapers, Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes newspapers articles, running results, press notebooks, autographed posters, and a quilt made from running t-shirts.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Sherrer was a sports running journalist and a competitive track, and road racer in distances ranging from the mile to the marathon; she co-founded the Finger Lakes Runners Club Women's Distance Classic and served as the Finger Lakes Runners Club Newsletter editor for nineteen years. She promoted women's running and encouraged women's team participation.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes newspapers articles, running results, press notebooks, autographed posters, and a quilt made from running t-shirts.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Sherrer, Diane; Cornell Masters Mile.; Finger Lakes Runners Club Women's Distance Classic.; Finger Lakes Runners Club.
Subjects:
Running.; Running--Training.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- the Diane Chronicles, 2007-2008 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Biathlon Gill Sharp, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Jim Hartshorne History (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Molly Huddle, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Molly Huddle, Magazine Articles, 2001-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Kip Keino Mile, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Track: FLRC Membership Lists, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Elmirathon, 1978-2002 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Women’s Distance Festival, 2000-2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- FLRC Board Retreat, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- New York City Marathon Crash, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Course Certification and Unfair Assistance Issues (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Masters Mile, 2006-2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Masters Mile, 1999-2005 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Masters Mile, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Ben Congdon, Boston Marathon & Barb Booker, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Jim Hartshorne Hall of Fame Entry Info. (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Interview Notes, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Interview Notes, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Interview Notes, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Interview Notes, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Interview Notes, 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Interview Notes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Interview Notes, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Interview Notes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Interview Notes, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Interview Notes, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Interview Notes, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Interview Notes, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Interview Notes, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Interview Notes, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Interview Notes, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Interview Notes, 2007 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Road Race Management, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Boston Marathon Press Notebook, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Boston Marathon Press Notebook, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Boston Marathon Press Notebook, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Boston Marathon tshirt, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Boston Marathon, 1979-2005 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Boston, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Boston Marathon, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Boston Marathon Program, 1997-2003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Pittsburgh Marathon Notebook, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Olympic Marathon Trials Notebook, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Boston Marathon Misc, 1999, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Misc. Race Results, 1975-2007 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Personal Scrapbook, 1979-1985 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Personal Scrapbook, 1988-1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Fitness Tips, 1970-1979 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Training Ideas, 1990-2005 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Women’s Sports, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Women’s Sports, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Women’s Sports, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Women’s Sports, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Women’s Sports, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Women’s Sports, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- The Pace Setter, 1989-1991 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- The Pace Setter, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- The Pace Setter, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Running News, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Outside, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- New England Runner, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- The Runner, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- The Runner, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- The Runner, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- The Runner, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- The Runner, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Runner’s World, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Runner’s World, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Philadelphia Half Marathon, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Marine Corps Marathon Results, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Boston Marathon Program, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Running News NYC Marathon Program, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Running Wild, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Running Times, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Running Times, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Track & Field News, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Life Magazine: Olympics, 1972, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Sports Illustrated, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Running Columns, August 1991-September 1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Running Columns, October 1992-January 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Running Columns, January 1994-September 1995 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Running Columns, September 1995-March 1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Running Columns, March 1997-June 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Running Columns, June 1998-April 1999 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Running Columns, April 1999-March 2000 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Running Columns, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Running Columns, February 2001-April 2002 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Running Columns, May 2002-May 2003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Running Columns, May 2003-August 2004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Running Columns, September 2004-October 2005 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Running Columns, October 2005-October 2006 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Running Columns, October 2005-November 2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Running Columns, December 2007-December 2008 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Running Columns, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Quilt made from running t-shirts (Box 8)
- Posters from running events, some are autographed (Box 9)
- Scrapbook, 1976-1981 (Box 10)
- Scrapbook, 1977-1982 (Box 10)
- Scrapbook, 1983-1985 (Box 10)
- Scrapbook, 1985-1989 (Box 10)
- Scrapbook, 1988-1989 (Box 10)
- Scrapbook, 1993-1994 (Box 11)
- Scrapbook, 1995-1997 (Box 11)
- Scrapbook, 2002-2005 (Box 11)
- Scrapbook, 2007-2008 (Box 11)
- Runners World, 1966-1979 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Runner Magazines, 1/80-4/80 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Runner Magazines, 5/80-8/80 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- The Runner, 4/80-7/82 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- The Runner, 8/82-12/82 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- The Runner, 1/84-4/84 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- The Runner, 5/84-8/84 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- The Runner, 9/84-12/84 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- The Runner, 1/85-4/85 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- The Runner, 1/86-4/86 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- The Runner, 5/86-8/86 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- The Runner, 9/86-12/86 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Runner’s World, 8/87-12/87 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Runner’s World, 5/87-8/87 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Women’s Sports, 1/77-4/77 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Women’s Sports, 5/77-8/77 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Women’s Sports, 9/77-11/77 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- The Marathoner, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- The Runner, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Runners World, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Runners World, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Runners World, 5/77-7/79 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Runners World, 8/79-10/79 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Runners World, 11/79-3/80 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- The Finish Line, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2/86-1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- FLRC Newsletter, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2005 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- FLRC Newsletter, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous Awards, No date (Box 15)
- Running related pamphlets, 1967-1986 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Exercise and Mental Health, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Poems, Races, etc, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Footnotes, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Letters and articles, 1996-97 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Red Baron, 1982-2001 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Race Results, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Race Results, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Race Results, 2000 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Race Results, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Race Results, 2002 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Elmira Area Races, 2003-09 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Elmirathon Tyvek Jacket, No date (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Race Results, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Running and Fitness News, 6/98-4/02 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- New York Running News, 1978-1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- New York City Marathon, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- New York The Runner, 1980-1983 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Runner Research News, 1986-1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Running Research, 1993-1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- TAC Times, No date (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Interview Notebook, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Interview Notebook, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- TAC Level I Biomechanics (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Aerobic Dance – A Visual Presentation, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Scrapbook, 1989-1991 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Scrapbook, 1998-1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Certificate of Appreciation, 1998-2006 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Lynn Jennings Photo Signed (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile Tapes (Box 17, Folder 9)
- RRCA National Volunteer Award, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Ed's Ultra Race Results, 1991-1994 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Danby Down and Dirty Results, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Masters National Track and Field Championships, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Empire State Games, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Family Fun Day at the Track, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Fillmore 5 and 10 Results, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Iroquois Trails Ultras, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Miscellaneous Documents, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Results, 1975-1985 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Results, etc., 1981-1985 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Results, 1986-1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Results, 1991-1999 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Results, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 Results, 2001-2006 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Hartshorne Memorial Masters Miles - DVDs, 2004-2006 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Ithaca Twilight, 1998-2005 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Races, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Finger Lakes Trail Runners Circuits, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- FLRC Publicity, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- FLRC Race Applications, 2008 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Forest Frolic 7K and 15K Trail Run Results, 1991; 1993; 1999 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Marathon to Marathon, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Master Marathon Results, 1991-1992; 1994; 1998-2000 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Ree-Way 10K, 2000-2001 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Running Injury Articles (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Snowshoe Race, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Skunk Cabbage Classic, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Skunk Cabbage Classic 1/2 Marathon, 10K Results, 1998-2007 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- FLRC's Star Test 10K (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Stonehead Ranking, 1998-2002 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Finger Lakes Trail Fifty Results, 1991; 1996; 2002 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Track Meets, 1976-1983 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Track Race Results, 1978 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- Track Race Results, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 34)
- Tom Bugliosi Trail Runs - 13K and 26K Results, 1992-1993; 1998-2001 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Triennial Finger Lakes Trail Relay, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Tortoise and Hare, 1996-2003 (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Trail Maps (Box 23, Folder 38)
- Training, Exercise, Fitness, Running Tompkins (Box 23, Folder 39)
- Utica Boilermaker Road Race - Signed Poster, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 40)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Logo, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Virgil Mountain Madness Trail Run Results, 1987-1988; 1992-2000 (Box 23, Folder 42)
- Woman's Distance Festival, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 43)
- FLRC Club Info (Box 23, Folder 44)
- All About ME! The Adventures of Diane (Box 23, Folder 45)
- Margret Betz (Box 23, Folder 46)
- Club History, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Yvette DeBoer (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Diane's Outstanding Club Member Jacket (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Joe Dubes (Box 24, Folder 4)
- To: Glamour "Protest," Concerning: Women in Sports (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Herb Engman (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Interview Tapes (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Joggers Cartoon Calendar, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Kelly LaBare, 1997-2001 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- FLRC Logo Entries Contest, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- The Marathon Epitome of Endurance and the Amateur Spirit (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Miss Polly - Phyllis Radke (Box 24, Folder 12)
- George Gavras Letters (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Terry Habecker (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Club History (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous DVDs, Photos, Results (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Hubert Morgan (Box 24, Folder 17)
- "Pre" (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Grete Waitz Interview, August 5, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Phyllis Radke Artwork (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Joe Reynolds Poems - Running, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Gill Sharp (Box 24, Folder 22)
- George Sheehan (Box 24, Folder 23)
- George Tillson (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Soul Connection: The Trowse Stories (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Diane Sherrer 50th Birthday Memory Quilt (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Joseph Streeter (Box 24, Folder 27)
- Survey and Retreat, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 28)
- Bill Roger Interview, July 15, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Cathy Troisi (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Lorrie Marnell Tily (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Christian Thompson (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Nate White (Box 24, Folder 33)
- Don Herres (Box 24, Folder 34)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Patch (Box 24, Folder 35)
- Skunk Cabbage Classic Totes Bag (Box 24, Folder 36)
- Authentic Gary Brudick Chocolate Syrup Water Bottle, 1990s (Box 24)
- Finger Lakes Running Club Bag (Box 25)
- Race T-Shirts
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 1990 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 1991 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 1997 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 1998 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 2000 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 2002 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 2003 (Box 18)
- Hartshorne Masters Mile T-Shirt, 2005 (Box 18)
- Virgil Monster Marathon T-Shirt, 199X (Box 18)
- Virgil Mountain Madness T-Shirt, 200X (Box 18)
- Virgil Mountain Madness T-Shirt, 2001 (Box 18)
- Empire State Games Singlet, 1989 (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Singlet, 1980s (early) (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Tank, 1980s (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Singlet, 2005 (Box 18)
- USA Masters Cross Country T-Shirt, 2004 (Box 18)
- Skylon Internation T-Shirt, 1982 (Box 18)
- Fred’s Team T-Shirt Signed (Box 18)
- WART T-Shirt (Box 18)
- Women’s Distance Festival In Memory Of Diane Sherrer T-Shirt, 2009 (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Snow Shoe T-Shirt, 1999 (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Snow Shoe T-shirt, 2000 (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Snow Shoe T-Shirt, 2001 (Box 18)
- Finger Lakes Snow Shoe T-Shirt, 2002 (Box 19)
- Nouveau Wine Race T-Shirt, 1985 (Box 19)
- Runners World Mens Olympic Trials T-Shirt, 1988 (Box 19)
- Avon Running T-Shirt, 197x (Box 19)
- Women on the move T-Shirt, 197x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Cap (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 197x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 197x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 197x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 197x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 198x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 198x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Tyvek Award Jacket, 1988 (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 199x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 199x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 199x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Tyvek Award Jacket, 199x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 199x (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 1990 (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 and 10 T-Shirt, 1990 (Box 22)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 1994 (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 1994 (Box 22)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 1996 (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 1999 (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 2000 (Box 19)
- Ithaca 5 & 10-15th (Box 20)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 bag, 2001 (Box 18)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 2002 (Box 18)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 2003 (Box 18)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 2004 (Box 18)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 2005 (Box 18)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 T-Shirt, 2006 (Box 18)
- Ithaca 5 & 10 Jacket, 2007 (Box 18)
- Skunk Cabbage Track Club T-Shirt (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirts (2) (Box 22)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 198x (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 1989 (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 199x (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 199x (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 1993 (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 200x (Box 19)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 200x (Box 20)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 2002 (Box 20)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 2003 (Box 20)
- Skunk Cabbage T-shirt, 2005 (Box 22)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 2006 (Box 20)
- Skunk Cabbage T-Shirt, 2007 (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Marathon T-Shirt, 199x (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Marathon T-Shirt, 197x (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Running Club BA Marathon T-Shirt, 198x (Box 20)
- Forge the Gorges T-Shirt, 200x (Box 20)
- Rec-Way 10k T-Shirt, 200x (Box 20)
- Rec Way 10k T-Shirt (Box 22)
- New York City Marathon Wind Jacket (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Trail Runs T-Shirt (Box 21)
- Ridge Runner Snow Shoe Shoe Sweatshirt, 200x (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club T-Shirt, 198x (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club T-Shirt (Box 22)
- Finger Lakes Cycling Club Sweatshirt (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Singlet, 197x (Box 20)
- Finger Lakes Runners Club Jacket, 198x (Box 21)
- New York City Marathon Rain Jacket (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 199x (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 1997 (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 1998 (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 2000 (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 2003-2005 (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 2009 (Box 21)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt, 18th (Box 22)
- Finger Lakes Fifties T-Shirt (Box 22)
- Finger Lakes Fifties 50K Finishes T-Shirt (Box 22)
- Freihofer’s Run for Women (Box 21)
- Freihofer’s Run for Women, 1993 (Box 21)
- Freihofer’s Run for Women, 1995 (Box 21)
- Freihofer’s Run for Women, 1998 (Box 21)
- New York City Marathon T-Shirt, 1979 (Box 22)
- New York City Marathon T-shirt (signed) (Box 22)
- Danby Down and Dirty T-Shirt, 199x (Box 22)
- Danby Down and Dirty T-Shirt, 2001 (Box 22)
- Danby Down and Dirty T-Shirt, 2002 (Box 22)
- Danby Down and Dirty T-Shirt, 2003 (Box 22)
- RRCA Women's Distance Festival T-Shirt, 1981 (Box 22)
- RRCA Women's Distance Festival T-Shirt (signed), 1981 (Box 22)
- Women's Distance Festival T-Shirt (Box 22)
- Women's Distance Festival T-Shirt, 2005 (Box 22)
- Women's Distance Festival T-Shirt, 2006 (Box 22)
- Women's Distance Festival T-Shirt, 2007 (Box 22)
- Fillmore 5K T-Shirt, 199x (Box 22)
- Fillmore 5K T-Shirt, 2005 (Box 22)
- Ed's Ultra T-Shirt-5th annual (Box 22)
- Monster Marathon T-Shirt, 199x (Box 22)
- Wineglass Twosome Marathon T-Shirt (signed), 1996 (Box 22)
- Ithaca Twilight Singlet (Box 22)